panaceatek.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy | Web Development Company | Panacea Infotech

Panacea respects the privacy of its clients. Therefore, our approach to privacy and data protection go beyond legal compliance. Privacy is one of the important parts of our culture and business value proposition. Protection of your privacy is one of our fundamental responsibilities; hence, it is imperative to us and our employees.

We ensure not to use your contact data such as your name and email address for personal use. Once you fill our registration form, we use your contact information only for sending our company’s information to you. We are publishing this privacy policy statement in order to show our commitment to safeguarding the privacy of information that you share with us.

## The Information we collect

When you order or request for our services, we need to know your name, email address, IP address and phone number etc. We may use this information to acknowledge your interest and requirements, process your order, notify you regarding your order’s status and provides you with better services.

## How we use the information

We use your personal information or the information that you provide us to complete your requirement/order. We do not sell, rent or share this information with any third-party except to the extent essential to accomplish that requirement/order.

If you show interest in our services and products and register with our site, we may use your email address or other contact information to inform you about our services and new products. To update our website and improve its design, we may use non-identifying information.

## Changes in the Privacy Policy

If any changes made in this privacy policy, you will see those changes on this web page. Therefore, you will always stay aware about how we collect and utilize your information. [Disclaimer](https://www.panaceatek.com/privacy-policy/)

We reserve all rights to change or modify this privacy policy anytime without informing anyone with prior notification. Thus, we advise you to review this privacy policy timely.

## Web Servers

With our web servers, we record and receive information from your browser automatically. This information includes your IP address, the time you visited our website, information about the page you requested etc.

## Cookies

We use cookies to gather aggregate information about site interaction and traffic to improve the user experience of the site. We may also take the help from third-party to track this information on the behalf of us.

## Third-party Links

You may find links to other sites on this website; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and content of these third-party sites. This privacy statement solely applies to information gathered by this site.

## Copyrights and Trademarks

The material available on this website is current and accurate. It is the sole property of Panacea Infotech Pvt. Ltd. We do not allow anyone to re-print the material available on this site without a prior written permission.

If you have any query regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at [info@panaceatek.com](mailto:info@panaceatek.com).
